Transliteration
Transcript
Translation
Original English lyrics
Language - Performer
The snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
English - Idina Menzel
not a footprint to be seen
Un royaume de solitude,
A kingdom of solitude,
A kingdom of isolation,
French - Anaïs Delva
ma place est là pour toujours
my place is here forever
and it looks like I'm the queen
French - Anaïs Delva
Der wind er heult so wie der Sturm ganz tief in mir
The wind, it howls, like the storm deep inside of me
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
German - Willemijn Verkaik
Het werd mij te veel, hoe ik mijn best ook deed
It was too much for me, no matter how hard I tried
Couldn't keep it in, heaven knows I tried
Dutch - Willemijn Verkaik
「Bié ràng tā men jìn lái kàn jiàn,
「別讓他們進來看見
Don't let them in or see
Don't let them in, don't let them see
Chinese Mandarin - Hu Wei Na (胡维纳)
zuò hǎo nǚ hái jiù xiàng nǐ de cóng qián.」
做好女孩，就像你的從前。」
Be a good girl, like you were before
Be the good girl you always had to be
Chinese Mandarin - Hu Wei Na (胡维纳)
Visa ingenting, vad du än gör,
Show nothing, whatever you do,
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
Swedish - Annika Herlitz
allting förstört!
everything is destroyed!
Well, now they know!
Swedish - Annika Herlitz
Ari no mama no
ありのままの
I will show you how I really am
Let it go, let it go!
Japanese - Takako Matsu (松たか子)
sugata miseru no yo.
姿見せるのよ。
I will show you how I really am
Can't hold it back any more!
Japanese - Takako Matsu (松たか子)
Libre soy, libre soy,
I am free, I am free,
Let it go, let it go!
Latin American Spanish - Carmen Sarahí
Libertad sin vuelta atrás.
Freedom without having to return!
Turn away and slam the door!
Latin American Spanish - Carmen Sarahí
Wszystkim wbrew, na ten gest mnie stać
Against everyone, I can afford this gesture
I don't care what they're going to say
Polish - Kasia Łaska
Jöjjön száz orkán,
Come hundreds of windstorms,
Let the storm rage on
Hungarian - Füredi Nikolett
és közben a szívemen ül a jég.
And meanwhile my heart is wrapped in ice.
The cold never bothered me anyway.
Hungarian - Füredi Nikolett
Desde la distancia,
It is the distance
It's funny how some distance
Castilian Spanish - Gisela
que pequeño todo es
how small everything looks
Makes everything seem small
Castilian Spanish - Gisela
I les pors que em dominaven
And the fears that dominated me
And the fears that once controlled me
Catalan - Gisela
per sempre han fugit!
have fled away forever!
Can't get to me at all!
Catalan - Gisela
Non è un difetto, è una virtù,
It's not a fault, it's a virtue
It's time to see what I can do
Italian - Serena Autieri
e non la fermerò mai più
and I won't hold it ever again
To test the limits and break through
Italian - Serena Autieri
Nae mamdaelo jayulobge
내 맘대로 자유롭게
I want to live freely
No right, no wrong, no rules for me
Korean - Park Hye-Na (박혜나)
sallae
살래
on my own
I'm free!
Korean - Park Hye-Na (박혜나)
Sad je kraj, sad je kraj,
Сад је крај, сад је крај,
It's over, it's over,
Let it go, let it go!
Serbian - Jelena Gavrilović (Јелена Гавриловић)
Na krilima vetra sam
На крилима ветра cам
I am on the wings of the wind
I am one with the wind and sky
Serbian - Jelena Gavrilović (Јелена Гавриловић)
Seoi6 jik6 jiu3 cyun4 sam1 gong2?
誰亦要全心講，
Who also wants to speak from the heart?
Let it go, let it go!
Cantonese - Jobelle Ubalde (白珍寶)
Mong4 diu6 zau6 tin1 bei2 go1
忘掉昨天悲歌
If I forget it, I'll be higher than the sky
You'll never see me cry
Cantonese - Jobelle Ubalde (白珍寶)
Estou aqui, e vou ficar,
Here I am, and here I'll stay,
Here I stand, and here I'll stay,
Portuguese - Ana Encarnação
venha a tempestade
let the storm come...
Let the storm rage on...
Portuguese - Ana Encarnação
Kuasaku buat hidup bercelaru
My powers make life go haywire
My power flurries through the air and to the ground
Bahasa Malaysian - Marsha Milan Londoh
Podvlastny mne morozy, lyod
Подвластны мне морозы, лёд
Frost and ice obey me,
My soul is spiralling
Russian - Anna Buturlina (Анна Бутурлина)
Nu chto za divnyy dar
Ну что за дивный дар
what a divine gift!
in frozen fractals all around
Russian - Anna Buturlina (Анна Бутурлина)
Og som krystaller står en tanke ganske klar
And one thought stands clear as crystal
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
Danish - Maria Lucia Heiberg Rosenberg
Shte spra da bada az
Ще спра да бъда аз
I will stop being captive to the past
I'm never going back
Bulgarian - Nadezhda Panayotova (??)
na minaloto plen
на миналото плен
I will stop being captive to the past
The past is in the past!
Bulgarian - Nadezhda Panayotova (??)
La den gå, la den gå,
Let it go, let it go,
Let it go, let it go!
Norwegian - Lisa Stokke
jeg skal stige lik solen nå
I shall rise like the sun, now
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
Norwegian - Lisa Stokke
Plòi òk maa, lêrk sôn ráyn
ปล่อยออกมา, เลิกซ่อนเร้น
Released, stop hiding,
Let it go, let it go!
Thai - Gam Wichayanee (??)
dèk dee mâi hĕn mee kâa.
เด็กดีไม่เห็นมีค่า
the good girl is worthless
That perfect girl is gone
Thai - Gam Wichayanee (??)
Je suis là, comme je l'ai rêvé!
I am here, like I dreamed it
Here I stand in the light of day
French - Anaïs Delva
En de storm raast door!
And the storm rages on!
Let the storm rage on!
Flemish - Elke Buyle
De vrieskou daar zat ik toch al niet mee.
The cold has never bothered me.
The cold never bothered me anyway.
Flemish - Elke Buyle