English
Flemish from http://youtu.be/tknUjV7e_Ec
[Google Translate back to English]
This place
Deze zaal
[This hall]
It's...
Als...
[If so ...]
It's like a memory from a dream.
Als een herinnering uit een droom
[As a reminder of a dream]
Dancing bears
Witte zwaan
[White swan]
Painted wings
Goud omringd
[Gold surrounded]
Things I almost remember
En nog steeds in mijn dromen
[And still in my dreams]
And a song someone sings
Klinkt een lied iemand zingt
[Sounds a song someone sings]
Once upon a December
Dat december zal komen
[That December, will come]
Someone holds me safe and warm
Houd me vast, zo word ik warm
[Hold me tight, so I'll be warm]
Horses prance through a silver storm
Bijna neem jij mij bij de arm
[Nearly you take me by the arm]
Figures dancing gracefully
Wals ik als beginneling
[I waltz as beginner]
Across my memory
Door mij herrinering
[In my memory]
Someone holds me safe and warm
Houd me vast, zo word ik warm
[Hold me tight, so I'll be warm]
Horces prance through a silver storm
Bijna neem jij mij bij de arm
[Nearly you take me by the arm]
Figures dancing gracefully
Wals ik als beginneling
[I waltz as beginner]
Across my memory
Door mij herrinering
[In my memory]
Far away, long ago
Geen verdriet, alles blinkt
[No sorrow, everything shines]
Glowing dim as an ember
En nogsteeds in mijn dromen
[And still in my dreams]
Things my heart used to know
Klinkt een lied iemand zingt
[Sounds a song someone sings]
Things it yearns to remember
'T blijven vage fantomen
[They remain vague phantoms]
And a song someone sings
Ik zie niet wie er zingt
[I do not see who sings]
Once upon a December!
Dat december zal komen
[That December, will come]