You don't have to protect me. I'm not afraid.
Please don't shut me out again.
Please don't slam the door
You don't have to keep your distance anymore
'Cause for the first time in forever
I finally understand
For the first time in forever
We can fix this hand in hand
We can head down this mountain together.
You don't have to live in fear
'Cause for the first time in forever
I will be right here
Anna.
Please go back home
Your life awaits
Go enjoy the sun, and open up the gates
Yeah, but...
I know.
You mean well, but leave me be
Yes, I'm alone
But I'm alone and free
Just stay away and you'll be safe from me
Actually, we're not
What do you mean, you're not?
I get the feeling you don't know
What do I not know?
Arendelle's in deep, deep, deep
deep snow
What?
You kind of set off an eternal winter everywhere.
Everywhere?
Well, it's okay, you can just unfreeze it.
No, I can't. I don't know how.
Sure you can. I know you can.
'Cause for the first time in forever
Oh, I'm such a fool! I can't be free!
You don't have to be afraid
No escape from the storm inside of me
We can work this out together
I can't control the curse!
We'll reverse the storm you've made
Anna, please you'll only make it worse!
Don't panic!
There's so much fear!
We'll make the sun shine bright
You're not safe here!
We can face this thing together
No!
We can change this winter weather
And everything will be all right
I can't!