It's Coronation Day!
The window is open!
So's that door!
I didn't know they did that any more
Who knew we owned 8,000 salad plates?
For years I've roamed these empty halls
Why have a ballroom with no balls?
Finally, they're opening up the gates!
There'll be actual, real, live people
It'll be totally strange
But wow! Am I so ready for this change!
'Cause for the first time in forever
There'll be music, there'll be light
For the first time in forever
I'll be dancing through the night
Don't know if I'm elated or gassy
But I'm somewhere in that zone
'Cause for the first time in forever
I won't be alone
I can't wait to meet everyone!
What if I meet The One?
Tonight, imagine me gown and all
Fetchingly draped against the wall
The picture of sophisticated grace
I suddenly see him standing there
A beautiful stranger, tall and fair
I wanna stuff some chocolate in my face!
But then we laugh and talk all evening
Which is totally bizarre
Nothing like the life I've led so far
For the first time in forever
There'll be magic, there'll be fun
I could be noticed by someone
And I know it is totally crazy
To dream I'd find romance
But for the first time in forever
At least I've got a chance!
Don't let them in
Don't let them see
Be the good girl you always have to be
Conceal, don't feel
Put on a show
Make one wrong move and everyone will know
But it's only for today
It's only for today
It's agony to wait
Tell the guards to open up
The gate
For the first time in forever
Don't let them in, don't let them see
I'm getting what I'm dreaming of
Be the good girl you always have to be
A chance to change my lonely world
Conceal
A chance to find true love
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
I know it all ends tomorrow
So it has to be today!
'Cause for the first time in forever
For the first time in forever
Nothing's in my way!