Transcript and translation
from f4KlRR_P9ug
Sung by Kasia Łaska
The snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
Na zboczach gór biały śnieg nocą lśni
On the mountain slope white snow glows at night
not a footprint to be seen
i nietknięty stopą trwa.
untouched by a single footprint.
A kingdom of isolation,
Królestwo samotnej duszy
Kingdom of lonely soul
and it looks like I'm the queen
a królową jestem ja.
and the queen's me.
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
Posępny wiatr na strunach burzy w sercu gra.
Somber wind on strings of storm plays in my heart.
Couldn't keep it in, heaven knows I tried
Choć opieram się to się na nic zda.
Although I'm leaning it won't pass.
Don't let them in, don't let them see
Niech nie wie nikt, nie zdradzaj nic,
Let no one know, Do not tell,
Be the good girl you always had to be
żadnych uczuć, od teraz tak masz żyć.
No feels, from now on you have to live that way.
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
Bez słów, bez snów, łzom nie dać się,
Without words, Without dreams, Don't let tears in,
Well, now they know!
lecz świat już wie.
but the world already knows.
Let it go, let it go!
Mam tę moc! Mam tę moc!
I have that power! I have that power!
Can't hold it back any more!
Rozpalę to co się tli.
I'll ignite what's smoldering.
Let it go, let it go!
Mam tę moc! Mam tę moc!
I have that power! I have that power!
Turn away and slam the door!
Wyjdę i zatrzasnę drzwi!
I'll go out and slam the door!
I don't care what they're going to say
Wszystkim wbrew, na ten gest mnie stać!
Everyone against, I can offer that gesture!
Let the storm rage on
Co tam burzy gniew?
so what storms rage?
The cold never bothered me anyway.
Od lat coś w objęcia chłodu mnie pcha.
For years, something is pushing me towards cold's embrace.
It's funny how some distance
Z oddali to co wielkie,
From far away big,
Makes everything seem small
swój ogrom traci w mig.
its magnitude loses quick.
And the fears that once controlled me
Dawny strach co ściskał gardło,
Old fear that clutched my throat,
Can't get to me at all!
na zawsze wreszcie znikł.
forever disappeared.
It's time to see what I can do
Zobaczę dziś czy sił mam dość,
I'll see today if I have enough power,
To test the limits and break through
by wejść na szczyt, odmienić los
to climb the top, change the fate
No right, no wrong, no rules for me
i wyjść zza krat, jak wolny ptak.
and get out from behind the bars, like a free bird.
I'm free!
O tak!
Oh yes!
Let it go, let it go!
Mam tę moc! Mam tę moc!
I have that power! I have that power!
I am one with the wind and sky
Mój jest wiatr, okiełznam śnieg.
Mine is the wind, I'll master the snow.
Let it go, let it go!
Mam tę moc! Mam tę moc!
I have that power! I have that power!
You'll never see me cry
I zamiast łez jest śmiech!
and instead of tears there's joy!
Here I stand, and here I'll stay,
Wreszcie ja, zostawię ślad.
Finally I, will leave a print.
Let the storm rage on...
Co tam burzy gniew?
so what storms rage?
My power flurries through the air and to the ground
Moc mojej władzy lodem spada dziś na świat.
Power of my ice today is salling on the world.
My soul is spiralling in frozen fractals all around
A duszę moją w mroźnych skrach ku górze niesie wiatr.
My soul in frozen fractals will let the wind carry it towards the top.
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
I myśl powietrze tnie jak kryształowy miecz.
and one thought wind cuts through like an icy sword.
I'm never going back
Nie zrobię kroku w tył,
I won't make a step back,
The past is in the past!
nie spojrzę nigdy wstecz.
I won't ever look back.
Let it go, let it go!
Mam tę moc! Mam tę moc!
I have that power! I have that power!
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
Z nową zorzą zbudzę się.
With new aurora I will awake.
Let it go, let it go!
Mam tę moc! Mam tę moc!
I have that power! I have that power!
That perfect girl is gone
Już nie ma tamtej mnie.
The old me is gone.
Here I stand in the light of day
Oto ja! Stanę w słońcu dnia.
This is me! Standing in the day light.
Let the storm rage on!
Co tam burzy gniew?
So what storms rage?
The cold never bothered me anyway.
Od lat coś w objęcia chłodu mnie pcha.
For years, something is pushing me towards cold's embrace.