Okay, can I just say something crazy?
I love crazy.
All my life has been a series of doors in my face
And then suddenly I bump into you
I was thinking the same thing, because, like...
I've been searching my whole life to find my own place
And maybe it's the party talking, or the chocolate fondue
But with you
But with you I found my place
I see your face
And it's nothing like I've ever known before
Love is an open door!
Love is an open door
With you
I mean, it's crazy
What?
We finish each other's
Sandwiches
That's what I was gonna say!
I've never met someone
Who thinks so much like me
Jinx! Jinx again!
Our mental synchronization
Can have but one explanation
You and I were just meant to be
Say goodbye
To the pain of the past
We don't have to feel it anymore
Love is an open door
Love is an open door!
Life can be so much more
With you
Love is an open
Door
Can I say something crazy?
Will you marry me?
Can I say something even crazier?
Yes!