I don't know if You can hear me
Or if You're even there
I don't know if You would listen
To a gypsy's prayer
Yes, I know I'm just an outcast
I shouldn't speak to you
Still I see Your face and wonder
Were You once an outcast too?
God help the outcasts
Hungry from birth
Show them the mercy
They don't find on Earth
God help my people
We look to you still
God help the outcasts
Or nobody will
I ask for wealth,
I ask for fame
I ask for glory to shine on my name
I ask for love,
I can possess
I ask for God and His angels to bless me
I ask for nothing
I can get by
But I know so many
Less lucky than I
Please help my people
The poor and downtrod
I thought we all were
The children of God
God help the outcasts
Children of God