Elsa?
Do you wanna build a snowman?
Come on, let's go and play
I never see you any more
Come out the door
It's like you've gone away
We used to be best buddies, and now we're not
I wish you would tell me why
Do you wanna build a snowman?
It doesn't have to be a snowman
Go away, Anna.
Okay, bye
The gloves will help.
See? Conceal it.
Don't feel it.
Don't let it show.
Do you wanna build a snowman?
Or ride our bike around the halls?
I think some company is overdue
I've started talking
To the pictures on the walls
Hang in there, Joan.
It gets a little lonely, all these empty rooms
Just watching the hours tick by
I'm scared.
It's getting stronger!
Getting upset only makes it worse. Calm down.
No! Don't touch me!
Please, I don't want to hurt you.
See you in two weeks!
Do you have to go?
You'll be fine, Elsa.
Your Highness.
Elsa?
Please, I know you're in there
People are asking where you've been
They say "Have courage", and I'm trying to
I'm right out here for you
Just let me in
We only have each other; it's just you and me
What are we gonna do?
Do you wanna build a snowman?