Summer?
Oh. I don't know why,
but I've always loved the idea of summer
and sun, and all things hot.
Really?
I'm guessing you don't have much experience with heat.
Nope.
But sometimes I like to close my eyes,
and imagine what it would be like when summer does come.
Bees will buzz, kids will blow dandelion fuzz
And I'll be doing whatever snow does in summer
A drink in my hand
My snow up against the burning sand
Probably getting gorgeously tanned
In summer.
I'll finally see a summer breeze
Blow away a winter storm
And find out what happens to solid water
When it gets warm
And I can't wait to see
What my buddies all think of me
Just imagine how much cooler I'll be
In summer!
The hot and the cold are both so intense
Put them together It just makes sense
Winter's a good time to stay in and cuddle
But put me in summer and I'll be a...
(puddle?)
Happy snowman!
When life gets rough
I like to hold on to my dream
Of relaxing in the summer sun, just letting off steam
Oh, the sky will be blue
And you guys will be there, too
When I finally do
What frozen things do in summer!
I'm gonna tell him.
Don't you dare.
In summer!