Transcript and translation
courtesy of mWNB5vrF8W4
Sung by Ágústa Eva Erlendsdóttir
The snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
Sjá snjóinn glitra á fjallinu í nótt
See the snow sparkle on the mountain tonight
not a footprint to be seen
Ekkert fótspor hér að sjá
No footprints here to see
A kingdom of isolation,
Eitt einsemdar konungsríki
A kingdom of isolation
and it looks like I'm the queen
Og ég virðist, drottningin
And I seem to be, the Queen
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
Vindurinn gnauðar eins og ólgan inni í mér
The wind blows like the turbulence inside of me
Couldn't keep it in, heaven knows I tried
Gat ei byrgt það inni en ég reyndi samt
Couldn't keep it in, but I still tried
Don't let them in, don't let them see
Hleyp þeim ei inn lát þau ei sjá
Be the good girl you always had to be
Vertu góða stelpan sem þú varst
Be the good girl you always were
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
Feldu, bældu, seg þeim ei frá
Hide, suppress, don't tell them
Well, now they know!
En þau vita það þá
But then they know
Let it go, let it go!
Þetta er nóg, þetta er nóg
This is enough, this is enough
Can't hold it back any more!
Get ei lengur haldið í mér
Can't hold it in any more
Let it go, let it go!
Þetta er nóg, þetta er nóg
This is enough, this is enough
Turn away and slam the door!
Ég sný burt og skelli á eftir mér
I turn away and slam the door
I don't care what they're going to say
Mig varðar ei Hvað þau segja við því
I don't care What they'll say about that
Let the storm rage on
Látið geysa storm
Let a storm rage on
The cold never bothered me anyway.
Því kuldinn hann hefur ei háð mér neitt
The cold hasn't bothered me anything
It's funny how some distance
Það er merkilegt hvað fjarlægð
It's interesting how distance
Makes everything seem small
Gerir allt svo ofursmátt
Makes everything so small
And the fears that once controlled me
Og hræðslan sem hafði tökin
And the fear that once had the control
Can't get to me at all!
Virðist missa allan mátt
Seems to lose all its power
It's time to see what I can do
Ég þarf að sjá hvað ég get gert
I have to see what I can do
To test the limits and break through
Og reyná verk mín umtalsvert
And experience my powers pretty much
No right, no wrong, no rules for me
Og boð og bönn ei halda mér
And rules and bans don't hold me back
I'm free!
Ég er frjáls
I'm free
Let it go, let it go!
Þetta er nóg, þetta er nóg
This is enough, this is enough
I am one with the wind and sky
Uppi í himni eins og vindablær
To the sky like the wind goes
Let it go, let it go!
Þetta er nóg, komið nóg
This is enough, enough
You'll never see me cry
Og tár mín enginn sér fær
And no one'll get my tears
Here I stand, and here I'll stay,
Hér ég stend Og hér ég verð
Here I stand And here I'll stay
Let the storm rage on...
Látið geysa storm
Let a storm rage on
My power flurries through the air and to the ground
Minn máttur þyrlast gegnum loftið niðrá jörð
My power swirls through the air down to the ground
My soul is spiralling
Mín sál er hringiða
My soul is upside down
in frozen fractals all around
úr frosnum brotamyndum gjörð
out of frozen fractals made
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
Ein hugsun kristalla sem ískalt sprengigos
[One thought that icy crystals explosive]
I'm never going back
Ég aldrei aftur sný
The past is in the past!
Það var sem eitt sinn var
It was like it once was
Let it go, let it go!
Þetta er nóg, þetta er nóg
This is enough, this is enough
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
Og ég rís eins og morgunsól
I rise like the sun on dawn
Let it go, let it go!
Þetta er nóg, þetta er nóg
This is enough, this is enough
That perfect girl is gone
Þessi þæga stelpa fór
This pleasing girl is gone
Here I stand in the light of day
Hér ég stend Ein um bjartan dag
Here I stand Alone on a bright day
Let the storm rage on!
Látið geysa storm
Let a storm rage on
The cold never bothered me anyway.
Kuldinn hann hefur ei háð mér neitt
The cold hasn't bothered me anything